export default [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: 'What does HTML stand for?',
        answers: ['Function ', 'File', 'Date', 'FileUpload'],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: ' To insert a JavaScript into an HTML page, which tag is used? ',
        answers: ['< script=’java’>', '< javascript>', '< script>', '<js>'],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: 'How does Java Script store dates in objects of Date type?',
        answers: ['The number of days since January 1st, 1900 ', 'The number of seconds since January 1st, 1970 ', 'The number of milliseconds since January 1st, 1970 ', 'The number of picoseconds since January 1st, 1970'],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: 'Which of the following is correct to write “Hello World” on the web page?',
        answers: ['System.out.println(“Hello World”)', 'print(“Hello World”) ', 'document.write(“Hello World”)  ', 'response.write(“Hello World”) '],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: 'Which of the following is the tainted property of a window object in Java Script? ',
        answers: ['Pathname', 'Protocol ', 'Defaultstatus ', 'Host'],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: 'Which attribute needs to be changed to make elements invisible?',
        answers: ['visibilty ', 'visible  ', 'invisibility', 'invisible'],
        correct: 0
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: 'Which of the following is used to capture all click events in a window?',
        answers: ['window.captureEvents(Event.CLICK);', 'window.routeEvents(Event.CLICK );', 'window.handleEvents (Event.CLICK); ', 'window.raiseEvents(Event.CLICK );'],
        correct: 0
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: 'Which of the following is not a valid JavaScript variable name?',
        answers: ['2java', '_java_and_ java _names ', ' javaandjava', 'None of the above'],
        correct: 0
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: 'What is negative infinity in Java script?',
        answers: ['Any of below', 'number in JavaScript, derived by dividing number by a negative number', 'number in JavaScript, derived by dividing number by zero', 'number in JavaScript, derived by dividing negative number by zero'],
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: 'Which of the following is a client-side Java Script object?',
        answers: ['File', 'Function', 'FileUpload', 'Time'],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        question: 'What is the alternate name for Java script?',
        answers: [' LimeScript ', 'Both a and d', 'ECMScript ', 'ECMAScript '],
        correct: 3
    }
]